fosteringsolutions.com 2017-07-07

# Privacy Policy - Fostering Solutions UK Fostering Agency

Fostering Solutions strongly values the online protection of all visitors to this site and takes your privacy very seriously. Here we explain the types of information that may be collected when using this website and the procedures we have in place to safeguard your privacy.

**Information collected on this website and how this is used:**

Our website is largely information based, although there are some area’s which may ask you to register your name, email address and other relevant personal information. This information is used by us to communicate with you in relation to the purposes of your request and is treated in accordance with the Data Protection Act of 1998. Occasionally the company may use this information to contact you regarding services or products we think may be of interest to you. If you would rather not receive this information, please contact us and we will make the necessary arrangements.

If you have submitted your CV to us via our careers website then we will use this information as our recruitment process progresses. We may contact you in the future as the company grows to inform you of relevant career opportunities and make your information available to managers across Fostering Solutions and its associated companies where relevant to recruitment purposes.

We do employ the use of cookies which help to provide us with statistical information on the usage of this website to refine our content and services further. 

**Protecting your information:**

Fostering Solutions takes pride in the safe handling and storage of all personal information. Information is stored in our databases where every reasonable care has been taken to ensure the security and confidentiality of the contents. The company’s internal procedures cover the storage, access and disclosure of this information and we will only ever release your information where required by law.

**Updating your details:**

You have a legal right to a copy of all your personal information held by the company and can make this in writing to us. You also have a right to correct any errors within that information and are encouraged to contact us to request this.

**Consent:**

By using this website you consent to the collection and use of your information by Fostering Solutions as set out in this policy. If we change our privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page. If, for any reason, you do not agree to such changes please contact us and we shall remove your details from our records.
